ILR School Public Information Center Publications /3062
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Public Information Center Publications
1965-1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3062
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
The Public Information Center's "Key Issues" and other publications.
7924630
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 15, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 13, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3059: ILR School Press Releases /3060: ILR School Foreign Visitor Information /3061: ILR School Reprints of Articles about the School /3063: ILR School Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR) Forum /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records /3066: ILR School Alumni News /3069: ILR School School Scrapbook /3072 PUBS: ILR School Miscellaneous Publications of the School /3070 mf(d): ILR School Publication "For Our Information" (F.O.I.) Digital from Microfilm /3071: ILR School Albany Extension Division Records
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Public Information Center.
7924630
- Employee Stock Ownership Plans (ESOPs), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Group Legal Services, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- New Applications of Collective Bargaining, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- An introduction to Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Right to strike in Public Employment, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Technical Reports Series, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Reference Memorandum. No. 1-, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Job Satisfaction - Key Issues, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Manpower information for effective Management - Key Issues, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Redifining the Environment, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Games and Simulations Industrial and Labor Relations Training - Key Issues, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Employment testing and Minority groups - Key Issues, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Coalition Bargaining - Key Issues, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Job Satisfaction - Key Issues, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- The lie Detector in Employment - Key Issues, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Sensitivity Training - Key Issues, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- White Workers and Black Trainees, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Supportive Services for Disadvantaged workers and Trainees - Key Issues, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- The Lie Detector in Employment - Key Issues, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)